A good morning, today is the first day of the week and we will
talk about trading. Look at this myth
WhatsApp number. On that day,
all the major indices remained closed in the green mark
except Bank Nifty.
If we focus on the light metro network and soil, we got the strongest
upward light that day. We got a
golden light on that day. All the other details are
called Sunday's mid-day discussion.
You can see that in the Sunday special video as well.
Try to see it here. At this time,
as much as possible, the clothes in the market are strong,
using such strong clothes, from
here if we focus
on the market of Japan, there has been a very good rise in the market of these units. There has been a
good rise in Taiwan. Also, if we talk about
SGX Nifty, we have
explained around these almost fronts.
As we discussed in the entire interview, we can
see the forces very soon. But forces can also
appear very soon from 460 to favorite levels. Therefore, it becomes
important to pay attention above these levels.
In such a market, how much will the people who have shot on
17th Tarzan get the appropriate solution?  The
market went up quickly. This is what happens.
If we are sitting after shorting the index
and all the global markets are
showing signs of a rise, then it can
back down. Overall, the volume can remain
quite good. Let's talk about oil. There is
profit booking going on here. Let's
talk about cattle and gas. This is flight and
golden silver. You are seeing a rise
and a lot of rise in silver. The
rise around the last question is continuing today. Focus on the
protectors, silver and other things. Next,
if we talk about the currency market,
after a good correction from the top, now gradually
some recovery is seen from the bottom.
And so, how much did we use today, it is
not that way or it is not in the green. All the
other festivals like Great Britain
or Physicians, you are seeing all of them in the green. It is
possible that tomorrow
we may see the scheme again in the green.
Focus on graphics and
AIDS symptoms from now on, when it is the
September subscription data, we are going to keep a
frozen eye on the test lab
data, so for three days.  The data is in
front of you, the rest is yet to be
created and data of some other sectors is going to be seen every day
that what action is taken from here on f5
and about a good bank, let's
talk accordingly, one day I had done the settings in my device
and till now I am on Jio net,
my net is seen going towards that bank,
hence our focus should definitely be on this money flow on this clock, if we
talk about its results, right now
starting around 150 and beat constable,
if we talk about sixteen in the coming few days, after that first
it will be
Himalaya sixteen and after that,
as it goes above that, then we will gradually become
happy here, but it
feels comfortable, after so much tension, there is
not much mileage, we will keep an eye on it
and also on the data, so let's
cover today's news, first of all,
what is the news that
Aamir is coming out from National Hospital and you have
heard the name of that company, then comments are coming from here,
a restaurant chain, we
know about the company, this is what companies say,
leverage on the wrist  You have done your like and
share through equity shares
through different minister's windows, from here the
company has raised some funds, it has collected there,
definitely the company needs funds, the
process about which is mentioned today, in this way, right
now the condition salary, a company like this,
for this, restaurant is suitable for China, a little
hips, sometimes quiet, in the meantime, a lot of time is for
signing, so from here definitely
they need something, so in such a situation, it is okay, if the
company gets any money from anywhere, then the
company is a good thing, so according to News 20,
you can keep an eye on it today,
next, if we talk about HPCL,
I work for the company, we
city, some of you might know about it, it is a
domestic telecom gear maker company, so from
here on Friday, comment on their behalf, it is
pimpled, did it receive
board approval, you can say
for this thing, tourist 750 cr7 ft
company, overall the companies which are trained, there is a
plan to raise 750 crores
and for this their  They have already
received approval from the board, through which they will
press it. So, don't let 327 chests and any
other security like Nikkei go anywhere,
just money should go. Overall, the company's
focus should be on other things like 9200
and situation alarms. It
fights along with other operations
and can
provide better services from some of its peers. Therefore, the
company's overall focus is
on advertisements from various sources. So, from here also,
on the basis of news, you are keeping it in focus today.
Next 9 news are on airlines. If
we first cover Reliance Industries,
finally, in trading, well, you
are mobile. In this, on one side, it went up, a
bridge in Kota city, plus Nifty
took it with it and settled from there. It is going
up today. The way it
saw a rally on the last day, see today also
and the rally can continue. Therefore, Reliance is in
focus. First thing, now the second news is
its highest Reliance
Strategic Business Venture.  No. 1, a
good achievement in quantity has been made by
egging it into life sciences
and the word of this heart is around 393 1000, so from
here definitely
all India
friends, we have started from here onwards, the focus will be on the states which will be under observation today, so
next9news is coming out,
news regarding ICICI Lombard is coming out, it
says that the companies were receiving,
they have got the power of the regulator, they have got it from the
President, or if we
talk about IRDA, the Insurance
Regulatory and Development Authority, they have got it
for the winner of the general
insurance business of Bharti AXA General, so they have got
approval from here through demerger, this
further news on this is coming out
next9news, coming out of Bank of India, what is this in it,
earlier the
holding of LIC in Bank of India
was 23.17 2%, after this, if we talk about its recent
holding in IP, LIC has got a
big additional of around 4.3 in 3.87  The
sentence has been increased once, so
in such a situation, the total which was 3.17 earlier has now become 7.05
cents, so overall LIC has
increased its holding in it, that much in the morning update,
we
tried to cover all the lifts, all the uses, to get extra you
can cancel Jordan, you will get it on the channel,
now you will get all the links, you will get the
telegram healing in the description
and you will also get the private tanker pass link,
you will get everything, check it once
before uploading the video, otherwise you
can subscribe to the regular Declare channel, thank you so much